

Justin Katic

GAMES PROGRAMMER

- Sydney, NSW
- justinkaticdev@gmail.com
- □ https://justinkatic.com/
- in Justin Katic
- 0418 814 568

ABOUT ME

I'm a games programmer who specializes in gameplay programming. I'm passionate about programming because I always get to learn something new and grow. I enjoy problem-solving and collaborative programming because it challenges me to push my limits. My goal is work on evolving tech within the industry.

SKILLS

Unity Engine

- Photon networking
- URP
- C#

Source Control

- Branching
- Pull requests
- Merging

Collaboration & Planning

- Sprints
- Standups
- Agile workflow

EXPERIENCE

GAME PROGRAMMER July 2021 - Present **Dead Bear Studio**

Demon King Steam

- Integration of network code and ensuring stability.
- Integration and publishing to Steam.
- Worked within Unity engine.
- Collaboration within a team of 7 from proof of concept to Gold.
- Identifying and solving bugs.

GAME PROGRAMMER Nov 2020 - Present

JEAH! Studio

Lich Legend Android Lich Legend IOS

- Operated as a solo programmer working with both artists and a designer.
- Put together a team to create a published project on both IOS and Android.
- Wrote highly maintainable, solid code, forming core framework.
- Implemented and tracked analytic data.

ASSISTANT TEACHER April 2020 - Present Academy of Interactive Entertainment

- Assisted faculty and staff by teaching classes, conducting orientation programs, and issuing transcripts.
- Educated students studying Certificate II game programming qualification.
- · Created lesson plans.
- · Worked both remotely and in class.

EDUCATION HISTORY

Feb 2021 - Dec 2021

Advanced Diploma of Professional Game Development, Specializing in Programming Academy of Interactive Entertainment

Feb 2020 - Dec 2020

Diploma of Digital and Interactive Games, Specializing in Programming Academy of Interactive Entertainment

Feb 2017 - Aug 2017

Certificate IV Game Design: Game Design
TAFE NSW - Illawarra